<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--

    Copyright (C) 2013 - 2019 the enviroCar community

    This file is part of the enviroCar app.

    The enviroCar app is free software: you can redistribute it and/or
    modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published
    by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
    (at your option) any later version.

    The enviroCar app is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
    WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General
    Public License for more details.

    You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along
    with the enviroCar app. If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/.

-->
<resources>

    <string name="help_headline_1">1. About enviroCar</string>
    <string name="help_content_1">This app is part of the Citizen Science platform enviroCar (<a href="www.enviroCar.org">www.enviroCar.org</a>). You can use it to collect and analyze test drives and provide the measured data as Open Data.\n\nenviroCar is currently in a beta phase. As a result, the software’s stability is not yet comparable to standards associated with mature software.\n\nWe welcome your feedback (enviroCar@52north.org)! Your advice and suggestions help us to improve the software.\n\n</string>

    <string name="help_headline_2">2. Getting started</string>
    <string name="help_headline_2_1">2.1. Login/Register</string>
    <string name="help_content_2_1">In order to take full advantage of the enviroCar app\'s functional range, you must have a user account for the enviroCar platform. This enables you to upload your tracks as Open Data and evaluate them using the website\'s various analysis tools.</string>
    <string name="help_content_2_1_enum_1">Click <b>\"Login/Register\" in the navigation menu.</b>.</string>
    <string name="help_content_2_1_enum_2">Fill in your user name and password in the following window.</string>
    <string name="help_content_2_1_enum_3">Then click <b>\"Login\".</b></string>

    <string name="help_headline_2_2">2.2. Select car type</string>
    <string name="help_content_2_2">Certain information is needed to calculate data from the car diagnostics. Click "car settings" on the dashboard to access the car manager. This is where you manage your car types.</string>

    <string name="help_headline_2_3">2.3. Connect OBD-II adapter</string>
    <string name="help_content_2_3">In order to record a track, you must connect the app to an OBD-II adapter. First pair the app with the appropriate adapter. Plug the OBD-II adapter in your car’s OBD-II port. Follow the Bluetooth adapter instructions for connecting your smartphone and the adapter. If Bluetooth has not been activated, you can turn it on here.</string>

    <string name="help_headline_3">3. Record track</string>
    <string name="help_content_3_1">The following four requirements must be fulfilled before you can start recording a track:</string>
    <string name="help_content_3_bullet_1">Activate Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="help_content_3_bullet_2">Activate GPS</string>
    <string name="help_content_3_bullet_3">Select car type</string>
    <string name="help_content_3_bullet_4">Select OBD-II adapter</string>
    <string name="help_content_3_2">Once these parameters have been set, click the <b>\"START TRACK\"</b> button on the dashboard to begin recording your track. Once the motor has been started, the OBD-II adapter placed within communication range and a connection to the car established, the app will display the speed control panel. \n\n<b>Please note:</b> the time display will begin once a stable GPS connection has been established. Measurements are recorded and saved only when the app receives valid GPS positioning information.</string>

    <string name="help_headline_4">4. Observe tracks</string>
    <string name="help_content_4_0">Click <b>\"My Tracks\"</b> in the bottom bar to get a list of all your tracks. This list is divided into local and uploaded tracks. Local tracks are those that have been saved locally, but not yet uploaded to the enviroCar server. Uploaded tracks are those tracks that have been uploaded to the enviroCar server and are available as Open Data. These tracks have been explicitly assigned to your account. Subsequently, you can download them to another device and query them.</string>
    <string name="help_headline_4_1">4.1. Track details</string>
    <string name="help_content_4_1">In order to view the track details, click on a track\'s map or select <b>\"Show Details\"</b> in the track\'s menu. This opens a track view containing the track’s most important attributes and statistics. You can view statistics and/or visualize an attribute on a map. Click on the blue graph symbol to view <b>\"Track Statistics\".</b> Select/change the attribute via the menu. Click on the map to visualize the attribute, CO2 for example. Change the attribute (phenomenon) by clicking on the white graph symbol in the lower left corner.</string>
    <string name="help_headline_4_2">4.2. Upload track</string>
    <string name="help_content_4_2">You must be a registered user and logged in to the app to upload your track data to the enviroCar server. Click on the menu in the upper right corner of the track to be uploaded in the <b>\"My Tracks\"</b> view and select <b>\"Upload as Open Data\"</b>. Wait until the app has successfully completed the upload. Use the upload symbol in the lower right corner to upload all tracks at once. Carry out various analysis on all uploaded tracks and compare your data with other user groups’ data on the enviroCar website.\n\n<b>Important note:</b> When you upload your enviroCar data, you agree to publish the data as anonymized, Open Data, under an open data license. User data and information, such as which tracks belong to which user, is hidden from other users.</string>

    <string name="help_headline_6">5. Problems and feedback</string>
    <string name="help_content_6">We welcome your feedback (enviroCar@52north.org)! Your advice and suggestions help us to improve the software.\n\nIf you discover any problems, please send us an issue report. Click on <b>\"Others\"</b> in the bottom bar and select <b>\"Report Issue\"</b>. Fill out the form and click <b>\"SEND REPORT\"</b> to the enviroCar Team. Please be as detailed as possible.</string>

</resources>
